Inter-University Case Program Records
Inter-University Case Program Records
- Microfilm
  - Correspondence, alphabetical
    - ICP, Bylaws: Unincorporated and Incorporated; Case Proposals, Procedures for; Explanation of Program; Future of Program: Queries, Replies and other correspondence; Member Lists: 1961-1963; News, Numbers 1 and 2; Operating Procedures for New Program; Report, Number 1, 1956; Suggestions for Case Writers (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Ideas for study and followup (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - International City Managers Association (ICMA) (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - K, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Kaufman, Herbert (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Kaysen, Carl (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Kriesberg, Martin (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - L, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Leiserson, Avery (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Mac, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Macmahon, Arthur (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Mc, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - M, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Maas, Arthur (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Marshall, Hubert (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Martin, Roscoe C. (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Masland, John (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Meeting: South Bend, 1953 (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Member Institutions Financial (Box 23, Reel 63-5)
    - Membership mailings (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Membership withdrawals (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Millett, John D. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - N, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - National Membership Committee Meetings 1 through 6 (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - National Committee for Educational Administration (NCEA) (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Non-member mailings, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - O, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - O'Leary, Paul M. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Olson, Emery E. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Ostrom, Vincent (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - P, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Public Administration Clearinghouse (PACH) (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - R, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Ransone, Coleman (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Reining Jr., Henry (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Riggs, Fred (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - S, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Schubert, Glendon (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Sharpe, Carlton F. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Sherwood, Frank (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Shipman, George A. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Short, Lloyd M. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - SSRC: First meeting of Committee on Public Administration, 1938 (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Stene, Edwin O. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Stone, Donald (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Syracuse University, 1952-1962; correspondence, 1952-1962; Financial compilations: biennial and quarterly, office records, central staff; health claims correspondence and insurance data; personnel service vouchers; salary authorizations and terminations; special documents and letters (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Teaching: Case summaries and teaching aids (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Theory projects (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Tillett, Paul (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Truman, David B. (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - U, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - V, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - W, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Wallace, Donald (Box 23, Reel 63-6)
    - Weidner, Edward W. (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - Wengert, E.S. (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - White, Gilbert (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - Wittenberg, Philip (libel lawyer for ICP) (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - Wood, Robert C. (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - X-Y-Z, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - Ylvisaker, Paul (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
  - Resources for the Future, Inc., Contracts; Correspondence: Fisher, Fox, Jarrett; Belisle, Eugene (Fall River Situation); Craine, Lyle E.; David, Martin (proposals); Honey, John C.; White, Gilbert; Wolf, Alfred C.; Interim Report, 10/15/54; Memoranda, comments, etc.; Progress Report (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
  - Published cases
    - CPAC Cases, alpha by title, A- Sa, Air Search through Sale of the Tankers (Box 23, Reel 63-7)
    - CPAC Cases, alpha by title, Se-TVA, Self-Insurance in the Treasury through TVA Ammonia Plant (Box 23, Reel 63-8)
    - ICP Cases, by case number, #1 - #50 (Box 23, Reel 63-8)
    - ICP Cases, by case number, #51 through #69 (Box 23, Reel 63-9)
    - ICP Cases, by case number, #70 through #77 (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
  - Inactive cases, correspondence
    - Asher (Geiger): European Payments (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Axinn: MSU Cooperative Extension Service (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Bock, E.A.: Atomic Energy Case (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Bolton: Resignation from Office of International Trade Fairs (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Bradley, Phillips: Syracuse Cases (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Buford-Piccard: Short Cases in State Administration (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Clapp, Martin C.: Puerto Rico (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Duffie, Lt. Col. Claire A.P.: Public Law 969 (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Frey, Frederick W.:Salk Vaccine Program (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Garceau, Oliver: Five Military Cases (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Goldberg, Edward: Albuquerque Personnel Board (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Gove, Samuel K.: Illinois Auditor (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Grove, J.W.:Civil Defense of Trafford Park (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Herring, Pendleton: Cases (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Hollister, Barrett: Ohio Conservancy (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Hyneman, C.S.: War Department Case (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Kamp, H.W.: Veteran's Administration (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Maass, Arthur: Erlanger Case (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Mann, Seymour: Broome County Airport (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Mansfield, Harvey: Food Stamp Plan (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Klaymen and Long (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Masland, John: USAAF Academy (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - McCleery: Prison Reform (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - McGee: Austin Annexation (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - McMullin, Carlton E.: Trouble in the Corporation Court (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Miner: P.O. Deficiency Appropriation (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Nigro, Felix: Warren Case (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - No Author: General Allen, What To Do About TOC (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Norton, John DeWitt: Economic Programming (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Olson, Arne: Guardian Life Controversy (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Olsen, David Martin: Potrero Hill (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Persico, Jos. E.: NYS Food Additive Bill (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Pilcher, Palmer: Desegregation in D.C. (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Presthus, R. Vance: Col. Layle Case (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Robinson, Mariana: Restitution of European Freight Cars (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Romani, Joh: Magsaysay vs. Recto (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Rourke, F.E.: Connecticut FEPC (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Rudolph, Lloyd: Transfer of the Pacific Islands (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Schaetzel, Robert: Transition in the State Department (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Scoble, Harry M.: Bennington School (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Sherwood, Frank: Barton Flats Budget Dispute; Budget as Plan and Control Device; Police Policy, Two Vignettes (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Snel, Dirk: Licensing Firearms in Philadelphia (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Snyder, Richard: Korean Decision (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Stratmon: Liberia Public Health Mission (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Swanson, Bert E.: Community Controversy; Electric Power Policy (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Tesler, Jules: Case of the 61's (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Tillett-Bock: New Jersey Budget (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Tillett-Presthus: Jackson Prison Riot (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Underwood, Kenneth: Cases on Religion, Ethics and Politics (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Warp, George: Minnesota Purchase of Arkansas Bonds (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Yee, Robert: Children's Treatment Program (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
    - Ylvisaker, Paul: Metropolitan Cases (Box 23, Reel 63-10)
  - The West German Foreign Serivice: A Study of German Diplomats Under Adenauer (Lewin, Dennis Meier), 1961; dissertation (Box 23, Reel unmarked)